

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER · EVENT STREAMING · CLOUD

231 Cocksfield Avenue, North York, ON, M3H 3T6 Canada

□ (+1) 226-505-8235 | **■** mayurhadole@gmail.com | **回** MayurHadole | **m** mayur-hadole

Summary_

Software Developer with experience in event driven systems. Proficiency in operating multi-region distributed streaming platforms like Apache Kafka on AWS and On-premise. Ample software development life-cycle experience exercised from start to finish along with prominent communication skills and constructive attitude.

Work Experience _____

BMO Financial Group

Toronto, Ontario, Canada

Jan. 2020 - Present

DEVELOPER

• Design, build, secure, implement and maintain Multi-data-center Kafka infrastructure.

- Build automation to provision, maintain, and monitor all aspects of the Kafka environment via infrastructure as code.
- To meet stringent Recovery Point Objective (RPO), converted traditional Kafka clusters to multi region clusters.
- · Helped build real-time streaming data pipelines to reliably get data between systems and applications.
- Identify bottlenecks and tune to optimize Kafka performance and throughput.
- Built real-time streaming applications Kafka streams that transform & react to streams of data.
- Conceived and wrote detailed software implementations while ensuring that their code adhere to the security, logging, error handling, and
 performance standards and non-functional requirements.
- · Automating on-boarding of clients to Kafka by developing CI/CD pipelines for Kafka Streams, Topics, ACLs, Schemas, Kafka Connectors etc.
- **Skills**:Application Development(Java, KafkaStreams, KafkaConnect, JUnit), Other(JSON, AVRO, WSDL, HTML, CSS3, JavaScript, Angular, Git, Ansible, Bamboo, Jira, Confluence).

Orbis CommunicationsHamilton, Ontario, Canada

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (CONTRACT)

Oct. 2019 - Dec. 2019

- Enhancement & bug fixes in jQuery/Java based product.
- Skills: Application Development (Java, Spring, JSP, Hibernate, SQL, JUnit, jQuery, JavaScript, HTML/CSS), Scripting (Bash, Python),
 Other (BitBucket, Jira, HTML/CSS).

TD BankToronto, Ontario, Canada

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Mar. 2018 - Jun. 2019

- Design & Develop Spring Batch jobs in Java using dependency management and build tool Maven.
- Develop SQL stored procedures to perform data intensive logic and Shell Scripts for file manipulation, Job dependencies etc.
- Skills: Application Development (Java, Spring Batch, JDBC, Hibernate, JUnit), Scripting (Bash, Python), Other (Jenkins, Bitbucket, SonarQube, Confluence, Jira, HTML/CSS).

Skills_

Programming Java, C/C++, Linux, MYSQL, Python, VHDL, Verilog

Big Data Confluent Kafka, Kafka Connect, Avro.

Web HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, Angular, Bootstrap Framework,Cloud AWS S3, AWS Secrets Manager, Serverless Compute (AWS Lambda).

DevOps Tools GitLab, GitHub, BitBucket, Ansible, Bamboo, Jenkins, Maven, Terraform, SonarQube

Languages English, Hindi, Marathi, Gujarati.

Education

Conestoga College Kitchener, Ontario, Canada

POST GRAD DIPLOMA IN EMBEDDED SYSTEMS DEVELOPMENT

BACHELOR IN ELECTRONICS & COMMUNICATION ENGINEERING

2016 - 2017

2016 - 2017

• Award: Dean's Honors List Recognition and first rank for Capstone project (IoT Horticulture Systems)

Government Engineering College

Gandhinagar, Gujarat, India

2012 - 2015

• Relevant Courses: C/C++ Programming, Verilog, VSDL, Communication Skills

N.G. Patel Polytechnic

Bardoli, Gujarat, India

2009 - 2012

DIPLOMA IN ELECTRONICS & COMMUNICATION ENGINEERING

• Award: Silver Medal (Recognition for Academic Achievement)

NOVEMBER 7, 2021 MAYUR HADOLE · RÉSUMÉ